(Im going full edit on this srt -minusone_t)
O-kay, 3-2- 1 action.
Hello everybody, it's me.
Ahmad today will be continuing
with Part 2!!!!!!!!!
This is not April fooling joking, by the
way. This is going to be all spectating
from hearing. Be sharing my
screen and the's going to be looking on
everything on Part 2 this like the RM(_ElectroT) war
but it's again this time it's a Stefan
war. So we're going to do something
special to the GC event.
If you want, you guys can react to the
first video. I recommend to follow the
series. This is going to be a long series (i dunno about that------)
and it's going to be very nice. So now
I'm going to be sharing my screen. Get i--
I'm gonna react to everything that is
going to be shown. Make sure
to- It's going to be very interesting.
We're going to have so much fun. This
is going to be a very nice. Videyo
Watch anywhere. Download it.
So looking, looking, looking.
We're having office meeting now with
Sammy and as you can see [SoundBoard]: Lucky Block.
[Ahmad]: Lucky block. It means that he can get
lucky and I can get lucky- *ping* This this [SoundBoard]: Lucky Block.
[Ahmad]: Vectorbyte is sleeping. So we'll
wait for him. [SoundBoard]: YUUUUUUUUUUU *beat* Souja boy i tell you
[Ahmad]: So we always for him to wake up
and then they will continue rage baiting
with/for us to which we will which will
have kreting and we have victoring and we
have ste-naaning because he's NINA 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥
And it always was an ninar
So, uh, it all started if he, if he,
if you didn't watch. I will give you a
rewind of Part 1, if you didn't know what
happened in Part 1. Um
Part 1 is where's where's
Stefan beginning being hating and
a lot of stopping. And,
and and a lot of start starting
happening things like war stuffing and
mooring and like Garegori 🔥 So if you
want, you can fall apart too. Right
now we have Part 2 (Real one i think) coming this
Tuesday or Wednesday. It's going to be
amazing. Make sure to follow the series.
Now let's begin into this.
So now we're going to discover into here.
Yes, Sir, Sammy?
All right, Sir, we'll do 5 minute
countdown for Sammy Boy.
If you don't actualling anything.
Oh wait, it's pairing right? Oh
shittings. Oh shitTINGS. No, no, no,
no, no-ing.
If you don't actually in **** managing. (<< W H A TTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT, i used apple music like lyrics censor so you dont know what i censored)
You will getting.
We'll get permanently
banned. Permit.
Band frrom.
The sabbing team? No, no, I'm
not joking, it's sab team.
Greeting. Warning. Oops-sing.
There we going 5 minuting. If he
doesn't answer then 5 minute-ing I'll.
Turn into egg I'll turn into an egg once
this video. You know that this version of
me is rare and I've never revealed my
face. But you know that this
series is limited time. You can only
watch it this September. Other episodes
are going to be premiering. Like how
parting to win?
It's-- ad--
September 13, boi
Sammy, do you not know??????????????????????????????????????
about trying? brooooooooooooooooooo september thirteening
Oh my God, I think it's fining. Anyways,
continue about what Stefan-o is about to
speak about. You guys know Part 1. We
have parting to win here. cret will
send all the videos, you guys can upload
it. Uhhh, uh. All thank
you to cret-ting for recording mi vidiIngs
like this. We'll be doing more. If you
want more, please subscribe to Vectorbyte (i writing to ahmad to end this recording because it was so late and it was like around 23:35 utc+3 in my time -TGC)
Help him reach 300 subscribers.
This is going to be a premiere (bye guys i doing alt+home)
on YouTu-- (in 0 seconds----------)